

PROFILE

Goal oriented web developer with strong commitment to collaboration and solutions-oriented problemsolving. Use various web design software to develop customer focused websites.

Committed to high standards of web design, user experience, usability and speed for multiple types of end-user. Successful at maintaining customer satisfaction through effective customer support.

Logical and result-driven web developer dedicated to building and optimizing user-focused websites for customers with various business objectives.

CONTACT

PHONE: 9346240703

WEBSITE:

https://elham13.github.io/ELMA/

EMAIL:

Elhamuddin.mahmoodi@gmail.com

GitHub:

https://github.com/elham13/

HOBBIES

Coding Playing Football Watching Movies Reading

ELHAMUDDIN MAHMOODI

Junior Web Developer

EDUCATION

Shir Khan High School

06/2003 - 10/2015

I graduated high school with a GPA of 97.44 and got many awards of appreciations.

University College of Science Saifabad

04/2017 - 07/2020

Graduated Bachelor of Computer Applications with a GPA of 8. Developed some cool projects during the college life.

Naresh IT

06/2017 - 07/2018

Completed full-stack web development with a great result.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelance Web Developer

02/2018 - Present

I develop and design web sites and web applications. I have many cool projects, refer to my GitHub.

Top in Town Software development intern

11/2018 - 05/2019

My responsibility was to work with the team and to take part in developing the java based web application in Top in Town company.

SKILLS

